So like every day I wake up and I'm like, nah, it can't get wilder.
And then it does.
CNN has partnered with a gambling app that lets you wager on current events and world events.
Basically, they are literally making betting around war, around starvation, around natural disasters, which at this point are unnatural disasters, etc.
You're literally betting on demise.
Remember in Gladiator how people would make bets on like which gladiator would beat the beast?
Now the people making the bets are the ones making the beasts.
We're the gladiators in the ring.
How quick before people are literally betting on whether or not they'll survive a situation, hoping that if they do, they'll get a payout.
We're in the squid games.
That's where we are.
That, that, that, that, that, I think, I think that's the most dystopian I've ever seen.
I think it is.
I, I think we've done it.
I think we've met the final boss of capitalism.
Betting on our demise.
You're damn rude, eh?
I think we've been playing.